http://www.tnbcfoundation.org/privacy

Triple Negative Breast Cancer Foundation Privacy PolicyLast Updated: November 29, 2012[ Download this policy as a pdf ]The Triple Negative Breast Cancer Foundation, Inc., a New Jersey State non-profit corporation (“TNBCF,” “we,” “our” or “us”), has created this Triple Negative Breast Cancer Foundation Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to describe our information collection, use and disclosure practices. The terms of this Privacy Policy apply regardless of whether you provide us with your Personal Information (as defined below) via our website located at www.tnbcfoundation.org (the “Website”) or via another means (e.g. telephone, regular mail or face-to-face). As set forth in more detail below, TNBCF will not sell, trade or share your Personal Information with any third party for marketing purposes without your permission.BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE WEBSITE AND/OR ANY OF THE PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES FEATURED ON THE SITE, AS OFFERED BY TNBCF AND ITS THIRD PARTY PARTNERS INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, OUR PERIODIC NEWSLETTER (COLLECTIVELY, “TNBCF SERVICES”), AS WELL AS MAKING A DONATION TO TNBCF, YOU AGREE TO THE PRIVACY POLICY IN ITS ENTIRETY INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION: (1) THE INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS MAY BE AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME; AND (2) THE TRANSFER, PROCESSING AND MAINTENANCE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN THE MANNER SPECIFIED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS MAY BE AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY IN ITS ENTIRETY, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS THE WEBSITE AND/OR USE THE TNBCF SERVICES.TNBCF IS NOT A COVERED ENTITY FOR PURPOSES OF THE HEALTH INSURANCE PORTABILITY AND ACCOUNTABILITY ACT OF 1996 (“HIPAA”), NOR IS THE INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU TO TNBCF CONSIDERED PROTECTED HEALTH INFORMATION UNDER HIPAA. AS SUCH, THE ADDITIONAL PRIVACY AND SECURITY PROTECTIONS AFFORDED TO CONSUMERS/PATIENTS UNDER HIPAA ARE NOT CONTEMPLATED BY, NOR CONTAINED WITHIN, THIS PRIVACY POLICY.THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT: You may be required to provide certain of your Personal Information to either TNBCF or its third party service providers when making donations, requesting communications and/or in connection with requesting other TNBCF Services (whether such requests or communications occur in person, via the Website, e-mail, direct mail or telephone). For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” refers to your: (a) name; (b) organization; (c) postal address; (d) telephone number; (e) e-mail address; (f) credit card information; (g) bank information; (h) other billing information; (i) certain medical-related information; and (j) any other information provided in connection with the applicable request and/or communication. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, items (f) through (i) shall be referred to as “Sensitive Information.” Please note that TNBCF does not, at any time, have access to the Sensitive Information that is submitted online. Sensitive Information that is submitted online is collected and processed by and through web pages and forms that are hosted and controlled by our third party service providers, and the collection and use of such Sensitive Information remains at all times subject to the privacy practices of our third party service providers.USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION: Where you request to be contacted in connection with the TNBCF Services, to receive our newsletter or to make a donation, we use the Personal Information that you make available to: (a) process your request for TNBCF Services or to make a donation; (b) respond to your questions or comments; and/or (c) send you our periodic newsletter. In addition, we may file your questions or comments for future reference. If you wish to stop receiving future communications from us, please see the “OPT-OUT/UNSUBSCRIBE” Section below.INFORMATION SECURITY: We endeavor to safeguard and protect our users’ Personal Information. When users make Personal Information available to us, their Personal Information is protected both online and offline (to the extent that we maintain any Personal Information offline). The collection of Personal Information, including Sensitive Information, is processed by and through a secure server. This means that Personal Information submitted via the Website or a web page hosted by one of our third party service providers is encrypted using industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) technology before transmission. Further, on secure Website pages, including web pages hosted by our third party service providers, the web address in the address bar at the top of the browser screen starts with an “https” instead of an “http.” Web pages that are used for collecting TNBCF donations are verified by GeoTrust, and the donation transactions are processed using Blackbaud Payment Services, which is PCI Compliant.Access to your Personal Information is strictly limited, and we take reasonable measures to ensure that your Personal Information is not accessible to the public. The servers that we store Personal Information in are kept in a secure physical environment. We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of Personal Information under our control. Please be advised, however, that while we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your Personal Information, no storage facility, technology, software, security protocols or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Computer hackers that circumvent our security measures may gain access to certain portions of your Personal Information, and technological bugs, errors and glitches may cause inadvertent disclosures of your Personal Information; provided, however, that any attempt to breach the security of the network, our servers, databases or other hardware or software constitutes a crime punishable by law. For the reasons mentioned above, we cannot warrant that your Personal Information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through the Website, or a web page hosted by one of our third party service providers, is at your own risk.All of our users’ Personal Information is restricted in our offices. Only employees or third party agents who need the Personal Information to perform a specific job are granted access to Personal Information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all end-user Personal Information. Employees not adhering to our policies are subject to disciplinary action.UNAUTHORIZED DISCLOSURE. TNBCF will comply with all federal and state laws relating to the security of Personal Information. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your Personal Information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.WHEN WE DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION: Personal information, including Sensitive Information, is shared among TNBCF staff and certain of our third party service providers (for example, our accountants) to process your donation(s) or contact you about the TNBCF Services and/or our ongoing work.Credit Card Transactions, Electronic Fund Transfers, Payments by Check or Money Order and On-line Transactions. TNBCF utilizes third party service providers to provide credit card, bank, payment and information processing services, to manage a donor database and to communicate with donors. If you choose to make a donation on-line, by phone, through the mail or by other means, the Personal Information provided will either be collected directly, or we will share that Personal Information with our contracted third party service providers. TNBCF requires that its third party service providers have in place privacy policies and practices consistent with this Privacy Policy; provided, however, that we cannot guarantee the privacy practices of our third party service providers.Corporate Restructuring. TNBCF may transfer your Personal Information to a third party successor in interest if we are involved in a transfer of control or sale of assets; provided, however, that if we are involved in a merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Website of any change in ownership or uses of your Personal Information, as well as any choices that you may have regarding your Personal Information.Legal Necessity. TNBCF may be required by subpoena, law or governmental body to disclose your Personal Information; provided, however, that, where permitted by applicable law, we shall provide you with e-mail notice, and opportunity to challenge the subpoena or required disclosure, prior to disclosure of any Personal Information pursuant to same.Improper Activity. TNBCF may disclose your Personal Information in the event that we believe that the Website and/or TNBCF Services is/are being or has/have been used in violation of any TNBCF policies or to commit unlawful acts.NO SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR MARKETING PURPOSES: TNBCF does not rent, sell, trade or share Personal Information for marketing purposes with anyone or any other purpose other than as expressly specified in this Privacy Policy.COOKIES: When an end-user visits the Website, we send one (1) or more cookies and/or gif files (collectively, “Cookies”) to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the applicable end-user’s computer or other device. A Cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience at the Website. To find out more about Cookies, please visit www.cookiecentral.com. We use Cookies to improve the quality of the Website and/or TNBCF Services.Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept Cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. To disable and reject certain Cookies, follow the instructions associated with your Internet browser. Even in the case where a user rejects a Cookie, he or she may still use the Website and most TNBCF Services.THIRD PARTY LINKS: The Website may provide links to, and certain TNBCF Services and data collection forms are hosted by, third-party owned and/or operated websites including, without limitation, the websites and web pages owned and/or operated by our third party service providers. TNBCF is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, web pages or entities. In some cases, you may be able to make a donation through one of their third-party websites. In these instances, you may be required to provide certain information, such as a credit card number, to register or complete a transaction at such websites. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and TNBCF has no responsibility or liability relating to them.USE BY MINORS: Visitors under eighteen (18) years of age (or the applicable age of majority, if greater than eighteen (18) years of age) are not permitted to use and/or submit their Personal Information by and through the Website and/or web pages hosted by any of our third party service providers. We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from visitors under eighteen (18) years of age (or the applicable age of majority, if greater than eighteen (18) years of age). We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.OPT-OUT/UNSUBSCRIBE: To opt-out of receiving any e-mail notifications and newsletters from us, you can follow the instructions at the end of the applicable e-mail message or contact us using the following methods:REGULAR MAIL:TNBC Foundation PO Box 204Norwood, NJ 07648EMAIL: info@tnbcfoundation.orgTELEPHONE: 646.942.0242Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for purposes of communicating information relating to your request for TNBCF Services, as well as to respond to any other inquiry or request made by you. To opt-out of receiving TNBCF Services-related and inquiry response-related messages from us (including the newsletter), you must cease requesting TNBCF Services and cease submitting inquiries to us, as applicable.DELETING AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION: At your request, we will inform you of what Personal Information we have on file for you. In addition, at your request, we will remove Personal Information that you have provided to us, or that we have collected. You may do so by contacting us using the methods described in the “CONTACT US” Section below; provided, however, that we ask individuals to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).Please be advised that deleting your Personal Information will limit our ability to contact you in connection with the TNBCF Services. If you wish to be contacted by us in connection with the TNBCF Services, you may not delete the Personal Information that we have on file for you.Please be further advised that, after you delete your Personal Information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.CHANGES TO PRIVACY PRACTICES: From time to time, TNBCF may revise its Privacy Policy to address changing technology, security measures and Website functionality. We strive to provide you with timely notice of these changes with an updated post. If the manner in which we use Personal Information changes, we will notify users by: (a) sending the modified policy to our users via email; and/or (b) by any other reasonable means acceptable under applicable state and federal law. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your Personal Information in this different manner and we will only use your Personal Information in this different manner where you opt-in to such use.CONTACT US: If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at: info@tnbcfoundation.org; call us at: 646.942.0242; or send mail to: TNBC Foundation, PO Box 204, Norwood, NJ 07648.FILING A COMPLAINT WITH THE FEDERAL TRADE COMMISSION: To file a complaint regarding our privacy practices, please visit: https://www.ftccomplaintassistant.gov/
What is TNBC
Living with TNBC
Newly Diagnosed
Living with Metastatic TNBC
Treatment Options
Survivorship
Caregivers
Spotlight Stories
Helpline
TNBC Foundation,
P.O. Box 204, Norwood,
New Jersey 07648, USA
TNBC Foundation© and Triple Negative Breast Cancer Foundation© are registered trademarks of Triple Negative Breast Cancer Foundation, Inc.
Main Menu
Helpline
Donate
What is TNBC
Living with TNBC
Living with TNBC
We have compiled helpful information and resources to assist you before, during and after treatment including information on caring for a loved one with triple negative breast cancer.
Learn more
Newly Diagnosed
Living with Metastatic TNBC
Treatment Options
Survivorship
Caregivers
Spotlight Stories
Publications
Webinars
Research
Research
The Triple Negative Breast cancer Foundation supports critical research and stays up-to-date on the latest information in the area of triple negative breast cancer.
Learn more
TNBC Foundation Research Grants
Medical Conference Updates
Clinical Trials
Forums
Forums
Connect with other TNBC patients, survivors and caregivers in our online forum community.
Learn more
Forum Topics
TNBC Talk : Survivors Needed
TNBC Talk : Breast Cancer Oncogene TRIM37 &amp;amp; How to Target It
We are dedicated to raising public awareness, supporting research and providing meaningful programs and services to the TNBC community.
We were founded in 2006 as a group of friends to raise awareness and support research in the area of triple negative breast cancer.
